Guide to the Park Slope Civic Council (PSCC) records BCMS.0083
Brooklyn Collection
- Series 2: Carl Kaiserman papers, 1970-2004
  - Sub-series 2.1: Meeting Materials, 1978-2002
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1987 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1987 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1988 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1989 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1991 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1992 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1998 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 2000 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Trustees 1997-98, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Trustees '98-'99, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 2001 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council meeting notes and materials], 2002 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - [PSCC introductory meeting script], circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Sub-series 2.2: Subject Files, 1946-2005; 1980-2004
    The sub-series is grouped by topic, which is the original order imposed by the creator.
    This sub-series includes correspondence, news clippings, blueprints, floor plans, and photographs and negatives related to zoning and development projects in Park Slope and the history of the neighborhood and its buildings and landmarks. The subjects in these files informed Kaiserman's work on historic district expansion, presentations on "Lost Mansions" and "Lost Theatres," and his advocacy for the community on development and zoning proposals.
    - What Style is it? [A Guide to American Architecture], circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - What Style is it? [A Guide to American Architecture], circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Hanan [, James], circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Litchfield Villa, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 21, Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Litchfield Villa, circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Litchfield Villa, circa 1998 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Litchfield Villa, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Childs [Residence], circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Hulbert [Mansion], circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 26, Box 22, Folder 16)
    - [Adams Residence], circa 2004 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - PS 107 Annual School Fair, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Lost Theatres, circa 1989 (Box 8, Folder 29, Box 22, Folder 15, Flat file folder 1 of 14)
      General
      Flat file folder includes blueprints of Pavilion Theatre.
    - Pavilion [Theatre], 1978-1999 (Box 8, Folder 30, Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Pavilion Theatre, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - 297 1st St., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Historic Resources, 1987-2002 (Box 8, Folder 33, Flat file folder 11 of 14)
      Flat file folder contains timeline of American Institute of Architects (AIA) torn out of an unknown publication.
    - Historic Resources, 1996-2002 (Box 8, Folder 34, Box 23, Folder 3)
    - PS [Public School] History, 1972-1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Montauk Club Site, 5094.48 9528, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 2, Box 23, Flat file folder 3 of 14)
      Flat file folder contains blueprints of the Montauk Club.
    - Montauk Club, circa 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - [Historic Building Research], circa 1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Landmarks, 1978-1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Greenstone/Landmarks, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Landmarks, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Landmarks, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - [Landmarks], 1979-2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Windsor Terrace Hi-Rise, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Lost Mansions, 1996-2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Expanded Historic District, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Materials and Symbolisms, 1983-2004 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Tilyou [George C.], 1966-2005 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Feltman [Charles], 1996-2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - [Financial Panic of 1873 / Eastlake Style of Furniture], 2004 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - [Origin of Park Slope Neighborhood Name], 2003 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - [South Brooklyn Board of Trade History], 2004 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Brooklyn Heritage Trail, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 19, Flat file folder 9 of 14)
      The flat file contains a color copy of a 1776 map of Brooklyn, photocopy of the 1766-1767 B. Ratzer map of Brooklyn with several modern sites noted, and photocopied atlas maps of Gowanus.
    - NY Methodist, 1996-2003 (Box 9, Folder 20, Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Churches, 1986-2002 (Box 9, Folder 21, Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Temples, 1983-1996 (Box 9, Folder 22, Flat file folder 8 of 14)
      The flat file contains RKT and B Garfield Temple renovations floor plan.
    - In the News / Above 9th Street, 1980-2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - In the News / South of 9th Street, 1988-2002 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - In the News: Prospect Park / Green-Wood, 1964-2000 (Box 9, Folder 25, Flat file folder 5 of 14)
      The flat file folder contains a Greensward Foundation newsletter, a Municipal Art Society publication, Prospect Park "Festival of the Orient" poster, and newsletters from the Friends of Central, Prospect, Cadwalader, Fort Greene, Druid Hill and Branch Brook Parks.
    - In the News: Prospect Park / Green-Wood, 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - [Park Slope Historic District Block-by-Block Description], circa 1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - [Park Slope Historic District Block-by-Block Description], circa 1985 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Histories [Prominent Buildings in Park Slope], circa 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1, Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Histories [Prominent Buildings in Park Slope], 1978-1996 (Box 10, Folder 2, Flat file folder 7 of 14)
      Flat file folder contains blueprints and Kaiserman's hand-drawn layouts of Park Cinema and Bob's Home Improvement Center.
    - 429 12th St. Garage, 1989-2003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 158-160 12th St. Vacuum Bag Factory Expansion, 1991-2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 158-160 12th St. Vacuum Bag Factory Expansion, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Redistricting, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 6, Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Zoning, New + Proposal Policy Info, 1985-1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Zoning/Housing, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Improved Dwellings for the Laboring Class, circa 1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Zoning/Housing, circa 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Zoning/Housing, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Zoning/Housing, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Fifth Avenue Committee, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - [Vale of Cashmere], circa 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - [Funding Neighborhood Programs], circa 1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - [News Clippings from Bob Makla], 1998-2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - [A Little News newsletter], 1990 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - [Phoenix, Brownstone Brooklyn's Hometown Newspaper], 1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - ["Requiem for an Elm" by Robert E. Murphy], 1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - ["Brooklyn's Great Park" by Richard T. Anderson], 1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - PSCC/Civic News 100th Anniversary, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - [13-15 Plaza Street West Development], 2001 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - [Raintrees Expansion], 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - [76 Fifth Avenue Renovation], 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - [571 Warren Street], 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - PSCC 90th Anniversary, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Gowanus Canal, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 27, Box 23, Folder 10)
    - [William B. Tubby Architecture Question], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - [Historic Districts Council Recent Activities], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - [Bricks + Brownstones Walking Tour re-launch], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - [Bloomberg housing revival news clippings], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - [Christmas tree recycling], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - [Atlantic Yards Development Project], 2004 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - [Atlantic Yards Development Project], 2004 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - [Park Slope Civic Council history], 1973-1996 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - [Brownstone Revival Committee], circa 1996 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - PSCC [South Brooklyn Board of Trade], 1946 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - PSCC History, circa 1996 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Historic District Expansion, 1977-2000 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - [Volunteer Involvement], 1992 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - [PSCC-sponsored activities], circa 1998 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - [Boreum Hill Association], circa 1998 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - [Historic sources], 1996-2004 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Zoning, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Raintrees, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Zoning, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Zoning, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Ansonia [Clock Factory], 1999 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Zoning, 2000-2004 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Zoning, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - [937-939 Union Street], 1986-2001 (Box 10, Folder 51, Box 24, Folder 2)
    - [Quality Housing Program], circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - [Community board notification from Department of Buildings], 2001 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - [Zoning for R6 Zone], circa 1985 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Maxwellton's Carriage House and Caretaker's Home, 1997-2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - IKEA at PSCC, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Second Round of Rezoning from Union to 15th Street, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Second Round of Rezoning from Union to 15th Street, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Street fair on PPW [Prospect Park West], 2001 (Box 18, Folder 27, Flat file folder 14 of 14)
      The flat file folder contains a map of Brooklyn published by the Brooklyn Tourism Council.
    - Historic District Issues, 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - [Downtown Brooklyn traffic calming project], 1999 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Red Hook garbage transfer, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Raintree Restaurant 8616, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Sub-series 2.3: Gowanus Expressway Project, 1987-2004
    Sub-series 2.5 Gowanus Expressway Project, 1987-2004, includes correspondence, meeting minutes, press releases, diagrams, and news clippings from Carl Kaiserman's involvement in community groups lobbying for a tunnel alternative to the Gowanus Expressway. Community groups represented in these materials include the Park Slope Civic Council, Revitalization of the Southern Area of the Slope (ROSAS), Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition, and the Gowanus Community Stakeholder Group.
    Historical
    The Gowanus Expressway, a part of Interstate 278, runs between the Verrazano-Narrows Bridge and the Brooklyn-Battery Tunnel in Brooklyn. In the 1990s, the New York State Department of Transportation (NYSDOT) started working on the Gowanus Expressway Project to find ways to address traffic congestion and structural deterioration. Community groups in the area, especially the Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition and the Gowanus Community Stakeholder Group, weighed in on the alternatives that the NYSDOT presented and largely supported a tunnel alternative to the Gowanus Expressway.
    - [Gowanus Community Stakeholder Group, tunnel alternative], 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Includes one CD. This CD is not available for research use.
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 2002 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 2002 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 2002 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 2002 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 2001 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 2001 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition], 2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition Lawsuit News Clippings], 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition], 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition], 2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition], 2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Task Force], 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - [Boston Expressway Project news clippings], 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - [ROSAS and PSCC Testimonials against Gowanus Expressway Project], 1999 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - [Tri-State Transportation Campaign], 1999 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition], 1999 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project, Tunnel Alternative Selection Process, Tunnel Studies Briefing Package], 1999 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Task Force], 1999 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Community Coalition], 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 1987-2004 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 1997 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - [Gowanus Expressway Project], 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Gowanus Expressway Reconstruction I-278, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Gowanus Expressway Reconstruction I-278 - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Gowanus Expressway Reconstruction I-278 - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Gowanus Expressway Reconstruction I-278 - Background Gen. Info, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Gowanus Expressway Reconstruction I-278 - Press Publicity, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Gowanus Expressway Reconstruction I-278 - Alternative Design, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Sub-series 2.4: 14th Regiment Armory, 1990-2004
    Sub-series 2.6: 14th Regiment Armory, 1990-2004, includes correspondence, meeting minutes, reports, flyers, news clippings, blueprints, and photographs related to re-use plans for the Armory, including as a women's shelter, a Human Resources Administration intake and evaluation center, a live performance space, and a hub for film shoots.
    The folder "Photos of Theater in 14th Reg.," circa 1993, includes photographs of Brooklyn Academy of Music's production of "Les Atrides" performed in the 14th Regiment Armory.
    The 14th Regiment Armory, also known as the Eighth Avenue Armory and the Park Slope Armory, is located Construction on the building completed in 1895 when the 14th Regiment of the New York State Militia used the space. In 1986, a Human Resources Administration (HRA) women's shelter occupied part of the building. The HRA planned to close the shelter and open an intake and evaluation center in 1990, but community backlash and the womens' refusal to leave the building kept the shelter open. In 1991, the shelter did close and in 1994, the city launched a study of how best to use the building with consultants from Pratt Institute and City University of New York. Around this same time, military presence was being withdrawn from the building and the city was renting out the space for film shoots.
    The Armory was officially given to the city in 1996. In 2010, a Prospect Park YMCA sports complex opened up in the space.
    - [14th Regiment Armory], 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - [14th Regiment Armory], 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - [14th Regiment Armory], circa 2003 (Box 11, Folder 37, Flat file folder 12 of 14)
      Flat file includes floor plans and blueprints of the 14th Regiment Armory and photocopies of atlas maps of the area around the 14th Regiment Armory.
    - [14th Regiment Armory], 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - [14th Regiment Armory], 1994-1999 (Box 12, Folder 1, Box 22, Folder 6)
    - [14th Regiment Armory], circa 1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Photos of Theater in 14th Reg., circa 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - [14th Regiment Armory news clipping and letters to the editor], 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - [14th Regiment Armory landmark status application], 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - [Correspondence regarding 14th Regiment Armory usage], 1990-2001 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - [14th Regiment Armory], 1993-2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - [Armory Studio newspaper articles], 1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - [14th Regiment Armory Women's Shelter], 1991-2004 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - [14th Regiment Armory], circa 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - [14th Regiment Armory], 1990-1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - [Meeting notes regarding 14th Regiment Armory usage], 1990-1994 (Box 12, Folder 12, Box 22, Folder 5)
    - [14th Regiment Armory], 1990-1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - [Towards Home: Rethinking Architecture for Transitional Housing], 1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - [14th Regiment Armory Shelter], 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Armory Meeting, April 11, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Sub-series 2.5: Revitalization of the Southern Area of the Slope (ROSAS), 1970-2001
    This Sub-series is in original order.
    Historical Note
    Revitalization of the Southern Area of the Slope (ROSAS) was founded in 1978 by business owners and residents in South Slope to be involved in the development of the neighborhood and commercial areas. ROSAS joined the Park Slope Civic Council in 2001.
    Sub-series 2.5 Revitalization of the Southern Area of the Slope (ROSAS), 1970-2001, includes meeting minutes and agendas, correspondence, notes, news clippings, and reports related to Carl Kaiserman's work with Revitalization of the Southern Area of the Slope (ROSAS). Much of the material covers the 7th Avenue Commercial Revitalization project in the mid-1980s, which repaired storefronts along 7th avenue, as well as ROSAS' merger with the Park Slope Civic Council in 2001.
    - ROSAS By-laws, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 22, Box 23, Folder 1)
    - ROSAS flyers, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - ROSAS Map back-up info, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 24, Flat file folder 2 of 14)
      Flat file folder contains Carl Kaiserman's hand-drawn map of Park Slope and South Slope.
    - [Friends of Prospect Park], circa 1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - [How to do Business in New York State guide], 1977 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - [The Committee for a Prospect Park Environmental Center], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - [Park Slope Human Service Directory], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - [ROSAS materials on housing], 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - [Street activity permit instructions], 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Historic analysis sources, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - [ROSAS application for recognition of exemption], 1981 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - [ROSAS stationery], circa 1981 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - RFP [ROSAS, request for proposal], 1985 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - [Request for proposals projection of induced development and construction], 1985 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - [ROSAS agendas and reports], 1985 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - [ROSAS booklets and public relations], circa 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - [ROSAS Commercial Revitalization Program], 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - [Van Brunt Post Office complaints], 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Historic analysis sources, circa 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - ROSAS, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - ROSAS, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - ROSAS, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - ROSAS, 1981-1996 (Box 17, Folder 8, Flat file folder 4 of 14)
      Flat file folder includes photocopy of atlas map of area around the 14th Regiment Armory.
    - [Seventh Avenue South Development Corporation Certificate of Incorporation], circa 1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - [7th Avenue Revitalization], 1986 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - [ROSAS Shopping Guide poster], circa 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - [ROSAS building surveys of vacant buildings], circa 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - [ROSAS Commercial Revitalization], 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - [Proposal, grant, and fundraising guidelines], circa 1985 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - [ROSAS Commercial Revitalization Program], 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 15, Flat file folder 6 of 14)
      Flat file folder contains photocopies of atlas maps of the area around 14th Regiment Armory.
    - [ROSAS Commercial Revitalization], 1986 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - [ROSAS Commercial Revitalization], 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - [ROSAS reports and notes], 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 18, Flat file folder 10 of 14)
      Flat file includes floor plan of unknown house with Carl Kaiserman's handwriting.
    - [ROSAS reports and notes], 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - ["A Survey of ROSAS Residents' Shopping Practices"], 1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - [ROSAS mailing list contacts], circa 1998 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - [ROSAS Community Service awards], 2000 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - [ROSAS activities], 2000 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - [ROSAS activities], 1999 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - [ROSAS activities], 1998 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - ROSAS LDC [Local Development Corporation] Gloria Fleischer, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - ROSAS LDC [Local Development Corporation] Gloria Fleischer - Proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - ROSAS LDC [Local Development Corporation] Gloria Fleischer, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - ROSAS LDC [Local Development Corporation] Gloria Fleischer - CB#6 [Community Board Six], 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - ROSAS LDC [Local Development Corporation] Gloria Fleischer - Politicians, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1985 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3, Box 22, Box 4)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1983 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - [ROSAS] Newsletters, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1989 (Box 18, Folder 11, Box 22, Folder 3)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 12, Box 22, Folder 2)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1991 (Box 18, Folder 13, Box 22, Folder 1)
    - [Park Slope and ROSAS maps], circa 1991 (Flat file folder 13 of 14)
      The flat file folder contains a photocopied atlas map bound by Sterling Place to the north, Windsor Place to the south, Prospect Park to the east, and 5th Avenue to the west.
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1994 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - [ROSAS meeting notes and materials], 1995 (Box 18, Folder 17)